neargeek.com 2006-05-13

# Neargeek Technical Solutions, LLC

Neargeek Technical Solutions Privacy Policy: 

What personally identifiable information is collected on this site? Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, e-mail address) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include receiving e-mails, newsletters or simply asking a question about Neargeek Technical Solutions. Near Geek Technical Solutions does not collect personal information from you unless you are a member. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Security Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Neargeek Technical Solutions employees on a 'need to know' basis. All Neargeek Technical Solutions employees must go through privacy training upon starting with NTS.

E-mail: All e-mail lists maintained by Neargeek Technical Solutions contain the names of people who have requested to be a member of NTS. The e-mail address collected by NTS will never be rented to outside firms for any purposes.

How does this site use cookies? NTS uses cookies to identify you when you log in. This cookie contains only the entered login information (e-mail address and password).

How does this site use ip address? NTS uses ip addresses for our reference and to help us guard against fraud.

Legal Disclaimer: We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Neargeek Technical Solutions.

For More Information: If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail us by clicking on contact us.
